Guide to the Consumer Reports. Editorial Department records, 1934-2015, bulk 1936-1997 RL.11863
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Publication Production Files, 1937-1994; 4
  - Source Materials, Proofs, etc., 1942-1994; 20
    - Salt and High Blood Pressure, 1984 (Box 49)
    - Search for the Right Pain Reliever, 1987; 2 folders (Box 42)
    - Search for the Right Pain Reliever, 1987 (Box 47)
    - Search for the Right Pain Reliever, 1987 (Box 49)
    - Snake Oil for the Oil Companies (Gasoline prices), 1974 (Box 42)
    - Snake Oil for the Oil Companies (Gasoline prices), 1974 (Box 47)
    - Snake Oil for the Oil Companies (Gasoline prices), 1974 (Box 49)
    - Sugar and artificial sweeteners, 1975-1979 (Box 42)
    - Television Networks Reject Airbag Commercial, 1972 (Box 42)
    - Truth About Calcium, 1988 (Box 43)
    - U.S. Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1974-1975 (Box 43)
    - U.S. Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1974-1975 (Box 47)
    - U.S. Post Office, 1961-1973 (Box 43)
    - U.S. Public Health Service, 1965-1972 (Box 43)
    - U.S. Supreme Court, 1947-1974 (Box 43)
    - U.S. Supreme Court, 1947-1974 (Box 47)
    - U.S. Supreme Court--Article, 1959; 2 folders (Box 43)
    - Unmaking of a Consumer Advocate (Consumer Protection Act), 1972 (Box 43)
    - Unmaking of a Consumer Advocate (Consumer Protection Act), 1972 (Box 47)
    - Vitamin Pushers, 1986; 3 folders (Box 44)
    - Vitamin Pushers, 1986 (Box 47)
    - Vitamin Pushers, 1986 (Box 49)